2024's Medical Alert Comparison\*

[Medical Alert Systems
=====================](https://www.medicalalertsystems.us/)

### MedicalAlertSystems.us Privacy Policy

Update effective February 10, 2016.

MedicalAlertSystems.us (“Company” or “We”), respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.  
  
This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website located at www.medicalalertsystems.us (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.  
  
This policy applies to information we collect:

* On the Website.
* In e-mail, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Website.
* When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
* Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using the Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.  
  
Children Under the Age of 13  
  
Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of the Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at admin@medicalalertsystems.us.  
  
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It  
  
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:  

* By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number (“personal information”);
* That is about you but individually does not identify you; and
* About your Internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:  

* Directly from you when you provide it to us.
* Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
* From third parties, for example, our business partners.

Information You Provide to Us. The information we collect on or through our Website may include:  

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
* Your responses to surveys we might ask you to complete for research purposes.

Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies. As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:  

* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data, and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
* Information about your computer and Internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party Website or other online services (behavioral tracking).  
  
The information we collect automatically may include personal information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:  

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
* Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:  
  
Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.  
  
Web Beacons. Pages of our the Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).  
  
Web Analytics. We may use Google Analytics or other analytics software to track aggregate and anonymous user behavior on our Website. To learn more, please review the document entitled “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps,” located at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.  
  
We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or that you provide to us.  
  
Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.  
  
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different Website and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.  
  
We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.  
  
How We Use Your Information  
  
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:  

* To present our Website and its content to you.
* To provide medical alert companies with your contact information for telemarketing calls, in compliance with the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (“TCPA”).
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please notify us by sending an email to admin@medicalalertsystems.us. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.  
  
We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.  
  
Disclosure of Your Information  
  
We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.  
  
We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:  

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Company about our users is among the assets transferred.
* To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:  

* To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information  
  
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:  

* Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending us an e-mail stating your request to admin@medicalalertsystems.us.
* Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your e-mail address used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by emailing us at admin@medicalalertsystems.us. If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions.
* Targeted Advertising. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by sending us an e-mail stating your request to admin@medicalalertsystems.us. We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s website: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices. Your web browser may have a setting that allows you to automatically send a “Do Not Track” message to the Website you visit. Our Website does not currently have technology to respond to such requests.

Accessing and Correcting Your Information  
  
You can review and change your personal information by sending us an email at admin@medicalalertsystems.us to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.  
  
Data Security  
  
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.  
  
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  
  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.  
  
Changes to Our Privacy Policy  
  
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website’ home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.  
  
Contact Information  
  
Questions or comments about this privacy policy and our privacy practices should be directed to us at admin@medicalalertsystems.us.  

\*Medical Alert Systems is a free online resource that offers valuable content and comparison features to consumers. To keep such resource 100% free for consumers, MedicalAlertSystems.us receives advertising compensation from the companies listed on this page. Such compensation impacts the location and order in which such companies appear on this page. All such location, order and ratings are subject to change. MedicalAlertSystems.us does not include all medical alert sites available to consumers in the marketplace. All reviews on this site are unbiased and objective, but if you request to be contacted by the [companies reviewed on this site](https://www.medicalalertsystems.us/terms.php#thirdparty), we may receive a commission. We are disclosing this in accordance with the FTC’s 16 CFR, Part 255: 'Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising. All trademarks remain property of their respective owners. Unless otherwise specified, no association between MedicalAlertSystems.us and any trademark holder is expressed or implied. No endorsement of MedicalAlertSystems.us is expressed or implied by the mention of such trademarks.

Copyright ©2024 Medical Alert Systems
